Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, records
circa 1957-2012
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Center for Latin American Studies
SC0185
71 Linear Feet (48 boxes)
The records include correspondence, minutes, memoranda, and other office files; budget records; general information regarding the Latin American Studies program; conference materials; grant files; course readings and bibliographies; and files on various University departments and committees that were major influences on the direction and administration of the program.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The records were received as administrative transfers from the Latin American Studies Program and the Center for Latin American Studies, 1978-2010.
Information about Access
Personnel files in Series 1 are restricted until January 1, 2057. Otherwise this collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Stanford University Institute of Hispanic-American and Luso-Brazilian Studies, authorized in 1958 and directed by Ronald Hilton, was reorganized in 1964 as the Latin American Studies Program under the authority of the Committee for International Studies. Today the mission of the Center for Latin American Studies, located in Bolivar House, is to support research and teaching on Latin America by the faculty and students of Stanford in all fields of study.
Description of the Collection
The records include correspondence, minutes, memoranda, and other office files; budget records; general information regarding the Latin American Studies program; conference materials; grant files; course readings and bibliographies; publications; and files on various university departments and committees that were major influences on the direction and administration of the program.
International studies; Latin America; Johnson, John J.; Romney, A. Kimball; Stanford University. Center for Latin American Studies; Siegel, Bernard J. (Bernard Joseph); Wirth, John D.; Stanford University. Latin American Studies Program; Terman, Frederick Emmons, 1900-1982; Spaeth, Carl B.; Hilton, Ronald
- Records, Series 1
  - Accounting Statements, Subseries 1
    - Checks Paid, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Checks Received, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - General Corespondence, 1961 Jul-1964 Oct (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Interdepartmental Requisitions, cormpleted, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Interdepartmental Requisitions, completed, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Interdepartmental Requisitions, completed, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Requisitions, completed, outside vendors, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Requisitions, completed, outside vendors, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Requisitions, completed, outside vendors, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Summer Quarter: Funds Available, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Transfer of Funds, 1962 Dec-1964 Oct (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budgets, Subseries 2
    - Hispanic - American Budgets, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Latin American Studies (LAS) Commitments, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - LAS Committments, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Pre-NDEA Account: 2-EBZ-701-94, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Budget Statements: VCP-041-94, 1966-1667 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Ford-LAS 0perating Budget,T-PDZ-652, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ford-LAS Operating Budget, 1-PDZ-652, Mexican-American Seminars, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Ford-LAS Operating Budget, I-PDZ-652, Budget Extras, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Ford-LAS Operating Budget, 7-PDZ-652, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Ford-LAS 0perating Budget, 1-PDZ-652, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Ford-Las Operating Budget, L-PDZ-652, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Ford-90, I-PEZ-602-94, Budget Statement, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Ford-90, 7-PEZ-6A2-94, Budget Statement, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Ford-90, I-PEZ-602-94, Budget Statement, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Ford-90, I-PEZ-602-94, Budget Statement, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Ford-90, I-PEZ-602-94, Budget Statement, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Ford-90, 1-PEZ-602-94, Budget Statement, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Ford-90, I-PEZ-602-94, Budget Statenent, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Ford Budget Reports
      - Ford Foundation Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Ford Foundation: New Grant, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Ford Foundation: Proposal, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Ford Foundation: Proposal, 1964 Jun (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Ford Foundation: Proposal, 1964 Sep (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Ford Foundation: Report and Supplemental Report, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, 1967; Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, 1967; Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, Statement of Needs, 1970 Jun 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Ford FOundation: Report, Ford 90 Grant, 1970 Feb 10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, Six Year Fiscal Report, Working Papers, 1971 Feb (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, Ford 90 Grant, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, Summary, 1971 May (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, Ford 90 Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Ford Foundation: Report, Ford 90 Grant, Final, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - NDEA Budget Statements
      - NDEA Budget Statenents, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - NDEA Budget Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - NDEA Budget Statememts, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - NDEA Budget Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - NDEA Budget Staiements, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - NDEA Budget Statements, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - NDEA Budget Statements, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - NDEA Budget Statements, additional, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - NDEA Budget Statements, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - University Budgets
      - General Funds, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - General Funds, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Mexican-American Seminar, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Presidential Contingency Fund, Mexican-American Seminar, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - General Funds, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Chicano Seminar, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Mexican American Bibiliographer, Special Account, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - General Funds, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - General Funds, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Sunmaries: Fund Statements, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Chicano Studies Institute: Proposal and Grant, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Chicano Studies Institute: Students Accepted, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Chicano Studies Institute: Alternates, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Chicano Studies Institute: Applicants Admitted who Dec1ined, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Chicano Studies Institute: Incomplete Applications, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Chicano Studies Institute: Rejected Applicants, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Committees, Subseries 3
    - Committee on International Studies (CIS)
      - CIS Proceedings, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - CIS Proceedings, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - CIS Proceedings and Correspondence, 1966 Sep-1968 Nov (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - CIS Proeeedings and Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - CIS Retreat, 1968 Mar 28-30 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - CIS Presidential Visiting Committee, First Meeting, 1968 Sep (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - CIS Notes From the Ford Foundation Luncheon, 1968 Oct 15 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - CIS Proceedings, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - CIS Proceedings, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - CTS Report: Presidential Visiting Committee, 1971 Apr (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Latin American Studies (CLAS)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - CLAS Report to President's Office and Committee on International Studies, 1966 Jun 29 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - CLAS Reports, memos (and ditto masters for memos), 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - CLAS Suggestions Regarding New Ford Grant, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1966 Mar-1968 Jun (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1970-1971. (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - CLAS Conferences and Visiting Professors, 1970 Jun 8-Jul 17 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - CLAS Proceedings, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Latin American Studies Association, Local Chapter (LASA)
      - LASA Proceedings, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - LASA Proceedings, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Research, Subseries 4
    - CIS Research Proposals, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - CIS Research Proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - John J. Johnson Research Proposals, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - LAS Faculty Research Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - LAS Faculty Research Proposal, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - LAS Faculty Research Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fellowships, Subseries 5
    - Foreign Area Fellowships: General Information, 1968-1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Foreign Area Fellowships, 1972 fall (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Fulbright Hays Faculty Grant and Visiting Professors, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Guggenheim Fellowships, 1968-1969. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Latin American Reaching Fellowships: Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Mabelle McLeod Lerqis Memorial Fund, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Mexico-Linco1n-Juarez Scholarships, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - National Endowment for Humanities, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - National Science Foundation: Division of Social Science Quarterly Grant List, 1979 Jul (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Organization of American States Fellowships: Applications, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Social Science Research Council: Fellowships and Grants, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Stanford-Guanabara Exchange, Summary of Activities, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation: List of Fellowships, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Graduate Division, Subseries 6
    - Information about Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Information about Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Information about Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hispanic-American and Luso-Brazilian Studies Institute, Subseries 7
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Crystal, Thomas, Corespondence, 1965 Jan-Aug (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General lnformation, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Personnel, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Reorganization, General Infornation Regarding, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hispanic-American Report: Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Hilton Resignation and Hispanic-American Report Suspension, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Staff Study on Latin American Studies at Stanford, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Summer Session, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Humanities and Sciences, Subseries 8
    - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Anthropology Department Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Department of Art and Architecture, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Comnunications Department, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Department of Economics, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Food Research Institute, 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - History Department, 1966 Apr-1968 May (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - History Department, 1968 Sep-1972 Aug (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - History Department, 1972 Sep-1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Linguistics Department, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Department of Music, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Political Science Department, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Sociology Department, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Department of Spanish and Portuguese, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Special Programs, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - International Agencies, Subseries 9
    - Degrees Awarded-Computer Program, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Field Staff Reports: American University, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Funding of Asian Studies in the U.S. (Robert E. Ward-Center for Research in International Studies, 1974 Jul 26 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Inter-American Social Development Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - International Council on Educational Development/Committee on the Future of International Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Committee on the Future of International Studies, 1972 Sep-1973 Mar (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - International Studies Advisory Group Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - International Studies: Future at Stanford, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - National Council on Education, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - National Defense of Foreign Language (NDFL), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - NDFL Fellowships, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - World Studies Data Bank, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Latin American Data Bank, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Social Science Research Council (SSRC), Lambert Survey, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - SSRC-LAS Meeting on Lambert Recommendations, 1972 Jul (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Latin American Studies (LAS), Subseries 10
    - Berkeley, U.C., Proposed Program with, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Bolivar House Appointments, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Calendars, Appointment, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Calenders, Appointment, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Latin American Studies (CLAS): General Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - CLAS: Finances, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - CLAS: Finances, Library Component, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - CLAS: Membership, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - CLAS: Minutes, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - CLAS: Personnel, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - CLAS: Planning for New Grant, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Core Seininar, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Directory of Latin Americanists at Stanford University, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Fellowships, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Foreign Area Fellowship Program, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Graduate School Policies, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Guanabara State University Exchange, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Guatemala Field Station, Professor Benjamin Pau1, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Law Studies, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Library Component, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - M.A. Program, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NDEA, Subseries 11
    - NDEA: Alliance for Progress Centers, Steering Committee, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - NDEA: Appointments, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - NDEA: Contracts, 1965-1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - NDEA: Course List, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - NDEA: Course List, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - NDEA: Course List, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - NDEA: Course List, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - NDEA: Expense Accounts, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - NDEA: General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - NDEA: Latin America Language and Area Center, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - NDEA: Library Xerox Charges, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - NDEA: Miscellaneous Memos, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - NDEA: Printing Department, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - NDEA: Draft, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - NDEA: Proposal, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - NDEA: Proposal(Draft), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - NDEA: Proposal(Copy), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - NDEA: Proposal for NDEA Center, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - NDEA: Proposal for NDEA Center, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - NDEA: Proposal for NDEA Center, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - NDEA: Purchase Orders, 1965-1974 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - NDEA: Quarterly Report, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - NDEA: Stores, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - NDEA: Summer Conference on Programs, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - NDEA: Summer Instructions, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - NDEA: Summer Proposal, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - NDEA: Summer Proposal, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - NDEA: Summer Proposal, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - NDEA: Summer Proposal, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Summer Technical Report, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Summer Technical Report, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Summer Technical Report, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Task Force, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Technical Report, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Technical Report, 1966 Jun 29 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Technical Report, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Technical Report, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Technical Report, Working Papers, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Technical Report, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Technical Report, Working Papers, 1970 Jun (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Technical Report, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Technical Report, Working Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Technical Report, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Technical Report, Working Papers, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Technical Report, Working Papers, 1971 Jul (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Technical Report, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Telephone, Telegraph, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Trips and Meetings, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - National Defense Foreign Languages (NDFL), Subseries 12
    - Fellowships, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Fellowships, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Fellowships, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Proposal, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Proposal, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Proposal, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Proposal, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Proposal, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Summary Report on Proposals Submitted to Washington, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Personnel: Faculty, Staff and Students, 1962-1972; Subseries 13
    - Appointments, Change in Status, etc., 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Faculty and Staff, 1962-1972 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Ambrose, Anne C. (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Aybar, Jose Manuel (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Barrett, Jeffrey William (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Barry, Thonas C. (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Bergquist, Magola (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Borrero, Gerardo (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Ciancutti, Caroline (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Day, Elizabeth (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Dean, Susan Long (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - DeFarrari, Laura Maria (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - DelaTorre, Laura (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - DosSantos, Anne M. (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Drake, Susan (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Erickson, Marcia (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Evans, Lynnae (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Fagelson, Laura (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Feiman, Gloria, Frances (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Fleischaker, Jacelaine (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Garcia, Consuelo (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Graff, Gary Wendell (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Hammond, Deborah (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Herlin, Margaret (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Hilton, Ronald (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Hunt, Lynn (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Jacobi, Robert de Greeff (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Jennings, Helene (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Johnson, Judith (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Kaplan, Patricia (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Kennitzer, Wi11iam (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Kirschner, Patricia Taylor (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Kreicher, Connie L. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Lippincott, Thomas P. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Loren, Frances. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Lutz, Christopher (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Lynch, Denis Laurence (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Lynn, Frances M. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - McMahon, Carole (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Mann, Ralph (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Meyfarth, Margie (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Montero, Martha Adelia (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Morris, David Jonathan (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Newborg, Kenneth (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Negro, Carol Susan (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Norrell, Daniel R. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Osborne, Duncan Elliott (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Pops, Stephen M. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Potter, Barbara J. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Powell, Lawrence C. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Powell, Trinidad (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Ross, Louis (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Savio, Charles John (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Seldow, Richard (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Shankman, Marsha (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Siegel, Eve (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Smith, Vincent (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Sowers, Marjorie (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Spector, Ursula (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Stallings, Barbara (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Stell, Pat (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Stowe, William (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Gerdes, James C. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Kostash, Janis Mary (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Smith, Frederick Alan (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Sonnenblick, Mark (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Svara, James H. (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Brinkmann, Sal1y (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Cason, James Caldwell (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Fleischer, David V. (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Semi-Monthly Payroll Voucher (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Publications, Subseries 14
    - Ambrose, Anne Conover, "The Failure of the Columbian National Front," M.A. Thesis, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Latin American Research Review: General Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Latin American Research Review: Board, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Morse, Richard M., The Urban Development of Latin America: 1750-1920, Orders Concerning, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Morse Book: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Morse Book: Reviews, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Research Grants, Subseries 15
    - CIS, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - LAS Faculty and Students, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Bonilla, Frank, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Caucian, Francesca, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Caucian, Frank, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Caucian, Frank, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Carnoy, Martin, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Coelho, Joaquim F., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Fagen, Patricia, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 58)